<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kyiv on Conreality Blog</title>
    <link>https://conreality.blog/tags/kyiv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kyiv on Conreality Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright> </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://conreality.blog/tags/kyiv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First Flight</title>
      <link>https://conreality.blog/2019/10/first-flight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://conreality.blog/2019/10/first-flight/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Team Conreality just wrapped up a fruitful visit to Kyiv, testing and bringing home our new XXL-sized paintball drone built in collaboration with our friends at &lt;a href=&#34;http://drone.ua/&#34;&gt;Drone.UA&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Needless to say, we attracted quite a crowd of spectators while field testing the drone outside the Drone.UA offices. Not only did neighbors leave their offices to come say hello, but even people driving by stopped and parked to come meet us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The drone is based on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dji.com/matrice600&#34;&gt;DJI Matrice 600&lt;/a&gt; heavy-lift hexacopter platform supplemented with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dji.com/ronin-mx&#34;&gt;DJI Ronin-MX&lt;/a&gt; gimbal. The payload of a paintball marker with its compressed air supply is our own design (and still a work in progress). Powered by six large batteries, we can remain airborne for about 20 minutes. There are separate pilot and trigger controls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want to thank Drone.UA owners Valerii and Fevzi, and all the staff who helped us&amp;ndash;in particular engineer Vladislav! And not only was this an outstanding engineering collaboration, but we are also proud to have introduced Drone.UA to the use of &lt;a href=&#34;https://bitcoin.org&#34;&gt;bitcoin&lt;/a&gt; when settling all expenses related to the project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We still have some more work to do on more precisely balancing the payload in the gimbal, but we expect to start fielding the drone in paintball games come spring 2020. In the meantime, our efforts are focused on the software for making this bird semi-autonomous and fun to play against&amp;mdash;from a safe distance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/pg/conreality/photos/?tab=album&amp;amp;album_id=2451125641839633&#34;&gt;full photo album&lt;/a&gt; from our first flight is available on &lt;a href=&#34;https://facebook.com/conreality&#34;&gt;our Facebook page&lt;/a&gt;, and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nnJPntLH4mA&#34;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; is on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCr3AK-eGQ2lgSE4Ew729nWQ&#34;&gt;our YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt;. More to follow as we put our new drone through its paces!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>